

# CONTACT

- 9899563941
- contact@deepak.myself
- Gonda, Uttar Pradesh-271123

## SKILLS

- Graphic Design
- · Visual Design
- Branding Design
- · Packaging Design
- · Book Cover Design
- Motion Graphics

## TOOLS

Design Tool 1
80%
Design Tool 2
75%
Design Tool 3
80%
Typography
85%
Print Design

85%

# **DEEPAK SHUKLA**

# **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

## PERSONAL INFO

I am a passionate Graphic & Branding Designer having expertise of 5+ years. I work closely with my clients in developing strong brand identities that define and exhibit values, and also professional visual entities to define your tone. I am a strong team player and a social butterfly.

# **EDUCATION**

Advance Diploma in Graphic Design 2015-2017

ICIT LBS GONDA

Bachelors of Design in Graphic Design 2012-2015

MSITM DEGREE COLLEGE GONDA

## **EXPERIENCE**

Social Media Manager 2020-Present
Studio Shodwe

- Led a team of 3 designers to develop digital media resources.
- Led an Ad campaign for 4 brands over a 6 month period in driving result-oriented growth.
- Developed 200+ digital and print graphics.
- Graphic Designer 2017-2021

Liceria & Co.

- Developed Branding and Packaging designs for 4 new brands.
- · Designed over 300 social media content.
- Derived visual quality identity and guidelines for brands.
- Other digital and print designs.

#### REFERENCE

 Muskan graphic & studio contact@deepak.myself

 Mishra studio - HR, Studio Shodwe mishra 2007@gmail.com 7379348620

8090122160